COTSEN4 COTSEN4
Cotsen Children's Library
- Lavinia Russ
  - Biography of the Dame of Sark, 1975
    Correspondence between Russ and McElderry regarding a proposed biography of the Dame of Sark for young readers. The contract for the work was cancelled after Russ traveled to the Isle of Sark for research and found that the family was opposed to her project, despite their previous indication otherwise. Includes a letter to Judy Taylor at Bodley Head discussing the family's refusal to let Russ write the book.
- Miscellaneous Papers
  - Andre Francois, "European '80 Correspondence since 8/8/80"
    Despite the original label, nothing in the folder is from 1980.
  - "Haas, Japan Trip 1981, Correspondence to remain in NY"
  - "Haas, OWL PRIZE, Japan Trip"
  - "Anglund, Confidential"
    Correspondence regarding coloring book rights and contract negotiations
  - "Joan Walsh Anglund, Foreign Rights Correspondence"
  - "Joan Walsh Anglund, Foreign Rights Chart"
  - "Anglund: British Edition of the Cowboy's Christmas and a Child's Book of..."
  - "Anglund: Brazilian Edition of the Cowboy's Christmas"
  - Looking at Art Series